const cards = [
  { question: "Which kind of animal is Kala, who takes care of the little Tarzan?", answer: "Gorilla" },
  { question: "Which disney cartoon is the only one to take place in Australia?", answer: "The Rescuers Down Under" },
  { question: "What does WALL-E's abbreviation 'LL' stands for?", answer: "Load Lifter" },
  { question: "Which original disney character has starred in a movie about Adolf Hitler?", answer: "Donald Duck" },
  { question: "Which kind of animal is Goofy?", answer: "Dog" },
  { question: "Which alias does Aladdin use when Genie turns him into a prince", answer: "Prins Ali Ababwa" },
  { question: "Which car model is Sally from Cars?", answer: "Porche Carrera" },
  { question: "Which Rock'n'Roll classic, has got its name after the road, that runs through the town in Cars?", answer: "Route 66" },
  { question: "Who is the only disney princess that isnt actually royalty", answer: "Mulan" },
  { question: "What relation does Prince Caspian and Miraz have?", answer: "Miraz is Caspians Uncle" },
  { question: "Who is the only disney princess, that was inspired by an actual person", answer: "Pocahonatas" },
  { question: "Which capital does Remy see as 'My City'?", answer: "Paris" },
  { question: "What was the first Mickey Mouse cartoon to be produced in color?", answer: "The Band Concert" },
  { question: "What does Pumba means in Swahili?", answer: "Dusty" },
  { question: "In 1929 Mickey Mouse spoke his first words, what were they?", answer: "Hot Dogs" },
  { question: "True or False, Mickey Mouse was not the first cartoon to recieve a star on the Holly Wood hall of fame?", answer: "false" },
  { question: "What is Mickey Mouse sisters name?", answer: "Amelia Field Mouse" },
  { question: "What does Koda do when Kenai tells him not to speak?", answer: "He sings" },
  { question: "Who was the only disney main character, that didnt speak throughout the entire movie", answer: "Dumbo" },
  { question: "What school did the characters of High School Musical attend", answer: "East High" },
  { question: "What was the name of Maleficents pet raven", answer: "Diablo" },
  { question: "What was the name of Ursulas two pet eels", answer: "Flotsam and Jetsam" },
  { question: "How many daugthers king triton have in The Little Mermaid", answer: "7" },
  { question: "How many doohinkeys does arial have in the song 'Part of your world'?", answer: "40 doohinkeys" },
  { question: "What fraternity did Mike Wazowski become a member of in Monsters University?", answer: "Oozma Kappa" },
  { question: "What was the name of the city where the movie Monsters Inc took place?", answer: "Monstropolis" },
  { question: "True or false, Jessie actually to Andy's mom", answer: "True" },
  { question: "Which pizza brand shows in Disney Pixar films", answer: "Pizza Planet" },
  { question: "what is there 6.469.952 of in 101 Dalmatines", answer: "spots" },
  { question: "What kind of dinosaur was Arlo in the movie 'The Good Dinosaur'", answer: "Apatosaurus" },
  { question: "In Monsters Inc what does the code '23-19' means?", answer: "'W-S' (White Sock)" },
  { question: "What does Mary Poppins needs every second tuesday?", answer: "A day off" },
  { question: "What is the name of Reilys imaginary friend in Inside Out?", answer: "Bing Bong" },
  { question: "What emotions potrait in Reilys mind in the movie 'Inside Out'?", answer: "Anger, Sadness, Joy, Disgust, Fear" },
  { question: "What is Winnie the Poo proud to be?", answer: "Fat (Poo quote 'I'm short, fat and proud of that')" },
  { question: "What was the name of Marlins wife in the movie finding Nemo?", answer: "coral" },
  { question: "In which other Pixar movie does the WALL-E company 'Buy'n'Large' make an appearance?", answer: "Toy Story 3 (As the brand of batteries for Buzz)" },
  { question: "Who is the youngest Disney princess", answer: "Snow White (14)" },
  { question: "Which Disney princess has a tattoo", answer: "Pocahontas" },
  { question: "In 'Wreck it Ralf' what is the name of game to which Vanellope Von Schweetz belongs?", answer: "Sugar Rush" },
  { question: "Name Goofy's son", answer: "Max" },
  { question: "How many fingers does Mickey Mouse have", answer: "4 fingers" },
  { question: "Name the seven dwafs", answer: "Duc, Grumpy, Sleepy, Happy, Bashful, Sneezy, Dupy" },
];
